armstrong.com 2016-03-11

# Armstrong Web Privacy Policy

En Español

Armstrong World Industries, Inc. ("Armstrong") strives to achieve the highest standards of integrity for every online visitor. When you register at the Armstrong Web site, we aim to respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth how we handle information we obtain from you and learn about you when you visit our Web site, including: 

  * The information we collect;
  * The choices that are available to you regarding how the information is used and to whom it is disseminated;
  * Your rights to access and correct or update your personally-identifiable information; and
  * Our pledge to have reasonable security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.  

If you have any questions or comments about Armstrong's Privacy Policy, please contact us here. 

**NOTICE: Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
Armstrong collects two types of information about you when you visit our site: personal information (including, by way of example only, your name, address, telephone number and email address) and non-personal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our site that you have visited and your IP address). 

**1\. Personally-Identifiable Information - What We Collect**

The only personally-identifying information we collect and store about you is the information that you choose to provide to us. 

**Your Personal Portfolio**

The Armstrong portfolio is an easy way to keep track of the Armstrong products you like. Visitors can establish a portfolio by submitting their name (required), physical and email addresses and telephone number (optional), and by choosing a password (required). To access the portfolio, visitors will be required to enter their username (a combination of their first and last names) and password. 

**Electronic Mail**

We will also gather your personally-identifiable information when you send us an email. We will use this information to respond to your email. We may also use the information to send you notifications about our service. 

When providing your email address to Armstrong, you agree to receive information from Armstrong and the Armstrong family of companies. We may provide you with updates on products and services by mail, fax, or email. We will not provide your email address to any third party companies. You may unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the link at the bottom of each email you may receive. This notice does not constitute an obligation by Armstrong to provide any specific information via email. 

**Sweepstakes and Contests**

From time to time, we may request information from you in connection with sweepstakes and contests we offer on our Web site. Participation in these sweepstakes or contests is completely voluntary; you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. 

Armstrong may co-sponsor sweepstakes and contests with other companies, in which case the user’s individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with these companies. We will request that these companies maintain the privacy of the registrants’ information. 

Nevertheless, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected when you visit our Web site. 

**Business Partners / Professional Visitors**

Business partners and professional visitors requesting access to specialized content areas of this Web site may be required to provide identifying information. In addition, business partners and professional visitors may be required to submit their Federal Express or UPS account numbers when placing an order on this Web site. 

**2\. Sharing Your Information**

We may share your personally-identifiable information with companies within the Armstrong family of companies.

We use outside shipping companies to ship all commercial orders, as well as all overnight shipments for consumer orders. If you order from us, we will share your personally-identifiable information with these companies to fulfill your order. We will also share our commercial customers’ Federal Express and UPS account numbers with these companies in order to fulfill commercial orders. 

An outside company responds to consumer and commercial requests for additional information about our products. We will share your personally-identifiable information with any such company in order to respond to your request. 

**3\. Non Personally-Identifiable Information: What We Collect**

We collect and use non-personally identifiable information about you in the following ways:

**Cookies**

At certain points in your visit to the Armstrong site, our server (or the servers of our unaffiliated service providers) may send a "cookie" file to your computer. Your Web browser may prompt you to accept this file unless you have set your browser preferences to accept all cookies automatically. Cookies are employed primarily as a service to our customers, to extend the relevance and responsiveness of the Armstrong site. We may link cookie information with any personally-identifiable information you provide us. 

**Other Non-Personally-Identifiable Information**

The Armstrong Web site may collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit, such as type of browser, operating system, domain name, or IP address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve" up Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you visit pages on Armstrong's Web site our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. This means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. IP address information is used only to improve the service of the Armstrong site, and is then discarded at the end of each session on our site. 

Armstrong also collects information through "referrers" and various environmental variables. A "referrer" is information the Web browser passes along to Armstrong’s Web server that references the URL from which you came. "Environmental variables" include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed our Web site, type of Web browser and operating system or platform used, the Internet address of the Web site you left to visit Armstrong, the names of the pages you visit while at our Web site, and the Internet address of the Web site you then visit. We collect all of this information to allow us to detect broad demographic trends, to provide information tailored to your interests and to enhance your experience on Armstrong’s Web site. Armstrong may store "referrer" information for a limited period of time prior to deleting this information. 

At times, the Armstrong website may use what are commonly referred to as "pixel tags," "web beacons," or "clear GIFs," including other similar methods (collectively, "Pixel Tags") to collect aggregated information about website usage. Pixel Tags allow Armstrong to measure the amount of users who have visited specific pages on our site and help determine the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. The information collected from Pixel Tags contains no personally identifiable information and is used for statistical analysis only. 

In certain situations, the use of Pixel Tags may be controlled by unaffiliated entities in order to manage programs or promotions. Armstrong cannot be responsible for third-party uses of Pixel Tags, however, when we are able; we employ our best efforts to assure that these unaffiliated entities do not collect personally identifiable information. 

In certain situations, the use of Pixel Tags and Cookies may be controlled by unaffiliated entities in order to manage programs or promotions. Armstrong cannot be responsible for third-party uses of Pixel Tags and Cookies, however, when we are able; we employ our best efforts to assure that these unaffiliated entities do not collect personally identifiable information. 

**Profiling**

To help us improve our Web site and to ensure that we make every effort to provide you with information and offers that are of interest to you, we may merge your personally-identifiable information with click-stream data and other data we have (including cookies and offline data). We will provide notice of this, as well as an opportunity to opt-out of it, at the time and place of information collection and before data is entered on our system. 

We may also develop a non-identifiable profile on you based on the pages within our site that you visit.

**4\. Links**

This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected when you visit our Web site. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Special Policy Regarding Information from Children Under Thirteen**

This Web site is not targeted to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly request personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 13 without parental consent. When we do receive such information, we delete it as soon as we discover it and do not use it or share it with third parties. 

**CHOICE**

Armstrong provides the following choices regarding the use of your information.

  * You may set your browser to reject cookies and to erase cookies that have already been placed on your hard drive. However, if you do so, your ability to navigate this site will be limited. 
  * You may choose not to provide us with any contact information.
  * If you would like us to manage your contact status or be removed from any of our on-line mailing lists, every email will contain an unsubscribe link, allowing you to unsubscribe from emails. 
  * If you do not want your personal or nonpersonal information merged with cookie and other information, you should not use the Armstrong Web site. 
  * If you would like Armstrong to delete any personal information you have provided, please send an email at [deletepersonalinfo@armstrong.com](mailto:deletepersonalinfo@armstrong.com) and write "Delete Personal Info" on the subject line. 

**ACCESS**

You may request to see personally-identifiable information that we have collected about you via the Internet to update it or to have factual inaccuracies corrected by clicking here. 

**SECURITY**

We make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security at our Website, you can send an email to [webmaster@armstrong.com](mailto:webmaster@armstrong.com).
